{
    "subject": "resource/Joan_Bennett",
    "predicate": "property/occupation",
    "object": "Actress",
    "human_readable": "Joan Bennett's occupation is Actress.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.8518748879432678,
            "question": "What was Joan Bennett's profession?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8076052069664001,
            "question": "Was Joan Bennett an entertainer?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8050750494003296,
            "question": "What is Joan Bennett's known profession?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.736415684223175,
            "question": "What kind of career did Joan Bennett have?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7349892258644104,
            "question": "Was Joan Bennett known for acting?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6410135626792908,
            "question": "Can you tell me about Joan Bennett's job?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5899951457977295,
            "question": "What role did Joan Bennett play in society?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5811065435409546,
            "question": "What was Joan Bennett famous for?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.37962833046913147,
            "question": "In what field did Joan Bennett work?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.34835758805274963,
            "question": "What did Joan Bennett do for a living?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Joan Bennett's occupation is Actress.",
            "html": "dbpedia_4674_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=In what field did Joan Bennett work?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4674_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What was Joan Bennett famous for?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4674_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What role did Joan Bennett play in society?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4674_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4674_125.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4674_34.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4674_40.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4674_45.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4674_5.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4674_50.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4674_64.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4674_67.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4674_70.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4674_88.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the structured JSON format with the answer:\n\n```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThis is because all four documents contain information about Joan Bennett, and in each document, it is mentioned that she was an American stage, film, and television actress. Therefore, the triple \"Joan Bennett's occupation is Actress\" is supported by the information in the documents."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\nThe documents provide multiple instances where Joan Bennett is described as an actress, thus supporting the triple that her occupation is that of an actress."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}